

susan vergnaud

Chicago, IL. 60608 • 773-459-3249

education

Columbia College Chicago

•B.A. Interactive Arts & Media with a concentration in Graphic Design

Digital Bootcamp

Web Development course

Design Lab

- Interaction Design course
- Research & Strategy course

summary

Creative designer and illustrator with experience in marketing and graphics. Currently responsible for planning, organizing and managing the design work-flow for various projects while working quickly and accurately, meeting tight deadlines and adhereing to brand consistency. I am dependable and self-motivated and can work well independently and as part of a collaborative group. I have excellent communication and orginaztion skills. I have strong UI/UX skills thay were developed through years of design experience and are continually expanding through online courses.

skills

- Excellent skills in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Acrobat, Microsoft Office
- Knowledge of Dreamweaver, After Effects, Final Cut Pro, PowerPoint, Flash, HTML, CSS, Sketch
- Platforms: Windows and Mac OS's.

experience

City of Chicago 5/2013-Current

Graphic Artist III

Chicago, IL

- Design and complete art work for major exhibitions and or events.
- Conceptualize thematic designs for illustrations on various publication large displays and events.
- Create and develop design ideas for various City departments.
- Provide clients creative direction while managing the progress of multiple projects from initial conception to the final product.
- Manage, tag and archive project and photo assets that reside on various servers.

National Restaurant Assoc. Education Foundation Senior Graphic Designer Chicago, IL 1/2013-4/2013

- Designed, edited and laid out event marketing/signage, promotional posters, banners, emails, flyers and brochures for two events- Annual Nationwide Invitational and the Annual golf classic event
- Created various foundation and event logos for print and web use.
- Managed and tracked the progress of multiple projects and kept up with various editing rounds.
- Work with the internal marketing communications team to revise and create all foundation materials regarding these two annual events.

Shared Marketing Services 1/2006-1/2013

Senior Graphic Designer

Chicago, IL

- Designed, edited and laid out web banners, emails, magazine ads, newsprint, brochures, promotional posters, postcards, logo design, flyers, icons, billboards.
- Created print, html templates and assests to be utilized for a mobile application.
- Conceptualized and designed a variety of print and web-related materials for local & national brands such as Audi USA/Canada, VW, BP, Harley Davidson, BP, New Balance, the Northface, Milgard and Ace Hardware.
- Edited animation, video, radio advertisements and created Photoshop website mockups.
- Proof print files before being sent out to outside vendors ensuring accuracy.
- Worked with account executives and the web dev. team to finish all the above tasks on time.

interests

I like to draw, sketch, paint and do various freelance projects. I am also involved with the Taproot Foundation doing pro bono design work for non for profit organizations.

portfolio

https://susanvergnaud.github.io • www.linkedin.com/in/susanvergnaud • susan.vergnaud@gmail.com